

Gabrijel Batista

Nationality: Croatian, Bosnian-Herzegovinian

(+387) 63919765

Date of birth: 06/03/1997

Gender: Male

Email address: batista_gabrijel1@hotmail.com

(S) Whatsapp Messenger: +38763919765

f Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100006246165850

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabrijel-batista1997/

Stack Overflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/13450559/gabrijel-batista

9 GitHub: : https://github.com/GabrijelBatista

• Address: Franjevačka 16b 16b, 88000 Mostar (Bosnia and Herzegovina)

ABOUT ME

I'm a bachelor or Computer Science on my way for master's degree with 3 years of expirience working as web developer. While studying in college I had the opportunity to get acquainted with many different technologies and I decided that I want to build a career as a web developer because that's my true passion. I mostly work with PHP and Javascript. My favorite frameworks are Laravel and Vue.js.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer (Freelancer)

[02/2019 - Current]

Backend Developer

QSD BiH [05/05/2021 - Current]

City: Mostar

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Master of Computer Science

Fakultet prirodoslovno-matematičkih i odgojnih znanosti [10/2019 – Current]

Address: 88000 Mostar (Bosnia and Herzegovina) https://www.fpmoz.sum.ba/index.php?lang=hr

Bachelor of Computer Science

Fakultet prirodoslovno-matematičkih i odgojnih znanosti [10/2015 – 10/2019]

Address: 88000 Mostar (Bosnia and Herzegovina) https://www.fpmoz.sum.ba/index.php?lang=hr

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Croatian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C2 READING C1 WRITING C2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Backend technologies

Laravel / PHP / MySQL / RESTful api

Frontend technologies

Vue.js / Vuetify / Vuex / JavaScript / CSS / HTML / Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap / JQuery

Other technologies

Clockify / Git / JSON / Trello / Laragon / BitBucket / Apache / Nginx / XAMPP/WAMPP server / JIRa / API Integrations / XML / Relational databases / Linux / AJAX / Object-Oriented Programming / SQL / Axios / Post man / Web Development / Github

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B